[SPEAKER_00]: to argue or fight among the couples?
[SPEAKER_00]: That was the question, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, about relationships.
[SPEAKER_00]: About relationships.
[SPEAKER_00]: Then maybe a good opportunity to meditate on patience also.
[SPEAKER_00]: or understanding, right?
[SPEAKER_00]: Also, Patoor Rinpoche's story, one time that one man is sort of meditating in the hermitage, and Patoor Rinpoche asked him, What are you meditating on?
[SPEAKER_00]: He said, Oh, I'm meditating on Zobah, patience.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then he whispered in his ear,
[SPEAKER_00]: People like you and me can fool people these days.
[SPEAKER_00]: And he got so angry, why are you coming here and bothering me?
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think, as a practitioner, as a Buddhist, as a practitioner, when things go well,
[SPEAKER_00]: then we don't really know how good our practice is or how much depth there is when in practice.
[SPEAKER_00]: So when circumstances arise, that's the time I think we have to use.
[SPEAKER_00]: So sometimes I think if you want to see how deep or how good you are, then some challenge may be.
[SPEAKER_00]: something that will stir up your negative emotions.
[SPEAKER_00]: And then you can see whether you can handle it or not.
[SPEAKER_00]: And some of the lojong practice, lojong teaching, it's almost like you have to look for trouble.
[SPEAKER_00]: Almost like that.
[SPEAKER_00]: Not really you poke on somebody, but you almost look for trouble, and you're fully ready to challenge any problem.
[SPEAKER_00]: So when the problem arises, you say, OK, now I can use my Lojong tactics.
[SPEAKER_00]: against the negative emotions.
[SPEAKER_00]: So this is the main purpose of practice, becoming a better practitioner.
[SPEAKER_00]: I have many friends, Westerners, Easterners, disciples of Khyentse Rinpoche, many.
[SPEAKER_00]: I don't really see them levitating or having a hollow on their head.
[SPEAKER_00]: But I've seen them becoming a better human being, less attached to the worldly life.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think that's the result of the practice.
[SPEAKER_00]: So I think the problem is, if you can look at it as a challenge, being a Buddhist practitioner, not much fear.
[SPEAKER_00]: And of course, being most important, not much hope and fear.
[SPEAKER_01]: Rinpoche, thank you so much for sharing the Dharma with us tonight.